https://www.kbgrp.com/about-us/terms-of-use

LoginOn-Line PaymentUpload 8879Upload to Staff
Terms of UseHome » About Us » Terms of UsePrint / PDF
ShareLast Modified: August 8, 2018
Acceptance of the Terms of Use
These terms of use are entered into by and between you and Kerkering, Barberio & Co., a Florida corporation (“KB”). The following terms and conditions (these “Terms of Use”) govern your access to and use of www.kbgrp.com, including any content, functionality and services offered on or through www.kbgrp.com (collectively, the “Website”).
Please read these Terms of Use carefully before you start to use the Website. By using the Website, you accept and agree to be bound and abide by these Terms of Use and KB’s Privacy Policy, found at https://www.kbgrp.com/about-us/privacy-statement, incorporated herein by reference (the “Privacy Policy”). If you do not want to agree to these Terms of Use or the Privacy Policy, you must not access or use the Website.
Changes to the Terms of Use
KB may revise and update these Terms of Use from time to time in KB’s sole discretion. All changes are effective immediately when KB posts them and apply to all access to and use of the Website thereafter.
Your continued use of the Website following the posting of revised Terms of Use means that you accept and agree to the changes. You are expected to check this page from time to time so you are aware of any changes, as they are binding on you.
Accessing the Website and Account Security
KB reserves the right to withdraw or amend the Website, and any service or material KB provides on the Website, in KB’s sole discretion without notice. KB will not be liable if for any reason all or any part of the Website is unavailable at any time or for any period. From time to time, KB may restrict access to some parts of the Website, or the entire Website, to users, including registered users.
You are responsible for:
making all arrangements necessary for you to have access to the Website; and
ensuring that all persons who access the Website through your internet connection are aware of these Terms of Use and comply with them.
To access the Website or some of the resources it offers, you may be asked to provide certain registration details or other information. It is a condition of your use of the Website that all the information you provide on the Website is correct, current, and complete. You agree that all information you provide to register with the Website or otherwise, including but not limited to through the use of any interactive features on the Website, is governed by KB’s Privacy Policy, and you consent to all actions KB takes with respect to your information consistent with KB’s Privacy Policy.
If you choose, or are provided with, a user name, password, or any other piece of information as part of KB’s security procedures, you must treat such information as confidential and you must not disclose it to any other person or entity. You also acknowledge that your account is personal to you and agree not to provide any other person with access to the Website or portions of it using your user name, password, or other security information. You agree to notify KB immediately of any unauthorized access to or use of your user name or password or any other breach of security. You also agree to ensure that you exit from your account at the end of each session. You should use particular caution when accessing your account from a public or shared computer so that others are not able to view or record your password or other personal information.
KB has the right to disable any user name, password, or other identifier, whether chosen by you or provided by KB, at any time in KB’s sole discretion for any or no reason, including if, in KB’s opinion, you have violated any provision of these Terms of Use.
Intellectual Property Rights
The Website and its entire contents, features, and functionality (including but not limited to all information, software, text, displays, images, video, and audio, and the design, selection, and arrangement thereof), are owned by KB, its licensors, or other providers of such material and are protected by United States and international copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret, and other intellectual property or proprietary rights laws.
These Terms of Use permit you to use the Website for your personal, non-commercial use only. You must not reproduce, distribute, modify, create derivative works of, publicly display, publicly perform, republish, download, store, or transmit any of the material on the Website, except as follows:
your computer may temporarily store copies of such materials in RAM incidental to your accessing and viewing those materials;
you may store files that are automatically cached by your Web browser for display enhancement purposes;
you may print or download one copy of a reasonable number of pages of the Website for your own personal, non-commercial use and not for further reproduction, publication, or distribution; and
if KB provides desktop, mobile, or other applications for download, you may download a single copy to your computer or mobile device solely for your own personal, non-commercial use, provided you agree to be bound by KB’s end user license agreement for such applications.
You must not:
modify copies of any materials from this site;
use any illustrations, photographs, video or audio sequences, or any graphics separately from the accompanying text; or
delete or alter any copyright, trademark, or other proprietary rights notices from copies of materials from this site.
You must not access or use for any commercial purposes any part of the Website or any services or materials available through the Website.
If you print, copy, modify, download, or otherwise use or provide any other person with access to any part of the Website in breach of the Terms of Use, your right to use the Website will cease immediately and you must, at KB’s option, return or destroy any copies of the materials you have made. No right, title, or interest in or to the Website or any content on the Website is transferred to you, and all rights not expressly granted are reserved by KB. Any use of the Website not expressly permitted by these Terms of Use is a breach of these Terms of Use and may violate copyright, trademark, and other laws.
Trademarks
KB’s name and logo, and all related names, logos, product and service names, designs, and slogans, are trademarks of KB or its affiliates or licensors. You must not use such marks without the prior written permission of KB. All other names, logos, product and service names, designs, and slogans on the Website are the trademarks of their respective owners.
Prohibited Uses
You may use the Website only for lawful purposes and in accordance with these Terms of Use. You agree not to use the Website:
in any way that violates any applicable federal, state, local or international law or regulation (including, without limitation, any laws regarding the export of data or software to and from the US or other countries);
for the purpose of exploiting, harming, or attempting to exploit or harm minors in any way by exposing them to inappropriate content, asking for personally identifiable information, or otherwise;
to transmit, or procure the sending of, any advertising or promotional material, including any “junk mail”, “chain letter” or “spam” or any other similar solicitation;
to impersonate or attempt to impersonate KB, a KB employee, another user, or any other person or entity (including, without limitation, by using e-mail addresses associated with any of the foregoing); or
to engage in any other conduct that restricts or inhibits anyone's use or enjoyment of the Website, or which, as determined by KB, may harm KB or users of the Website or expose them to liability.
Additionally, you agree not to:
use the Website in any manner that could disable, overburden, damage, or impair the site or interfere with any other party's use of the Website, including their ability to engage in real time activities through the Website;
use any robot, spider, or other automatic device, process, or means to access the Website for any purpose, including monitoring or copying any of the material on the Website;
use any manual process to monitor or copy any of the material on the Website or for any other unauthorized purpose without KB’s prior written consent;
use any device, software, or routine that interferes with the proper working of the Website;
introduce any viruses, trojan horses, worms, logic bombs, or other material which is malicious or technologically harmful;
attempt to gain unauthorized access to, interfere with, damage, or disrupt any parts of the Website, the server on which the Website is stored, or any server, computer, or database connected to the Website;
attack the Website via a denial-of-service attack or a distributed denial-of-service attack; or
otherwise attempt to interfere with the proper working of the Website
Monitoring and Enforcement; Termination
KB has the right to:
take appropriate legal action (including, without limitation, referral to law enforcement) for any illegal or unauthorized use of the Website; and
terminate or suspend your access to all or part of the Website for any or no reason (including, without limitation, any violation of these Terms of Use).
YOU WAIVE AND HOLD HARMLESS KB AND ITS AFFILIATES, LICENSEES, AND SERVICE PROVIDERS FROM ANY CLAIMS RESULTING FROM ANY ACTION TAKEN BY ANY OF THE FOREGOING PARTIES DURING OR AS A RESULT OF ITS INVESTIGATIONS AND FROM ANY ACTIONS TAKEN AS A CONSEQUENCE OF INVESTIGATIONS BY SUCH PARTIES OR LAW ENFORCEMENT AUTHORITIES.
Reliance on Information Posted
The information presented on or through the Website is made available solely for general information purposes. KB does not warrant the accuracy, completeness, or usefulness of this information. Any reliance you place on such information is strictly at your own risk. KB disclaims all liability and responsibility arising from any reliance placed on such materials by you or any other visitor to the Website or by anyone who may be informed of any of its contents.
The Website may include content provided by third parties, including materials provided by other users, bloggers and third-party licensors, syndicators, aggregators, and/or reporting services. All statements and/or opinions expressed in these materials, and all articles and responses to questions and other content, other than the content provided by KB, are solely the opinions and the responsibility of the person or entity providing those materials. These materials do not necessarily reflect the opinion of KB. KB is not responsible, or liable to you or any third party, for the content or accuracy of any materials provided by any third parties.
Changes to the Website
KB may update the content on the Website from time to time, but its content is not necessarily complete or up-to-date. Any of the material on the Website may be out of date at any given time, and KB is under no obligation to update such material.
Information About You and Your Visits to the Website
All information KB collects on the Website is subject to our Privacy Policy. By using the Website, you consent to all actions taken by KB with respect to your information in compliance with the Privacy Policy.
Linking to the Website and Social Media Features
You may link to our homepage, provided you do so in a way that is fair and legal and does not damage our reputation or take advantage of it, but you must not establish a link in such a way as to suggest any form of association, approval, or endorsement on our part without our express written consent.
Links from the Website
If the Website contains links to other sites and resources provided by third parties, these links are provided for your convenience only. This includes links contained in advertisements, including banner advertisements and sponsored links. KB has no control over the contents of those sites or resources and accepts no responsibility for them or for any loss or damage that may arise from your use of them. If you decide to access any of the third party websites linked to the Website, you do so entirely at your own risk and subject to the terms and conditions of use for such websites.
Geographic Restrictions
The owner of the Website is based in the state of Florida in the United States. KB provides the Website for use only by persons located in the United States. KB makes no claims that the Website or any of its content is accessible or appropriate outside of the United States. Access to the Website may not be legal by certain persons or in certain countries. If you access the Website from outside the United States, you do so on your own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws.
Disclaimer of Warranties
You understand that KB cannot and does not guarantee or warrant that files available for downloading from the internet or the Website will be free of viruses or other destructive code. You are responsible for implementing sufficient procedures and checkpoints to satisfy your particular requirements for anti-virus protection and accuracy of data input and output and for maintaining a means external to our site for any reconstruction of any lost data. KB WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGE CAUSED BY A DISTRIBUTED DENIAL-OF-SERVICE ATTACK, VIRUSES, OR OTHER TECHNOLOGICALLY HARMFUL MATERIAL THAT MAY INFECT YOUR COMPUTER EQUIPMENT, COMPUTER PROGRAMS, DATA, OR OTHER PROPRIETARY MATERIAL DUE TO YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE OR ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE OR TO YOUR DOWNLOADING OF ANY MATERIAL POSTED ON IT OR ON ANY WEBSITE LINKED TO IT.
YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE, ITS CONTENT, AND ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. THE WEBSITE, ITS CONTENT, AND ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE ARE PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS, WITHOUT ANY WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. NEITHER KB NOR ANY PERSON ASSOCIATED WITH KB MAKES ANY WARRANTY OR REPRESENTATION WITH RESPECT TO THE COMPLETENESS, SECURITY, RELIABILITY, QUALITY, ACCURACY, OR AVAILABILITY OF THE WEBSITE. WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, NEITHER KB NOR ANYONE ASSOCIATED WITH KB REPRESENTS OR WARRANTS THAT THE WEBSITE, ITS CONTENT, OR ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE WILL BE ACCURATE, RELIABLE, ERROR-FREE, OR UNINTERRUPTED; THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED; THAT THE WEBSITE OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES IT AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS; OR THAT THE WEBSITE OR ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE WILL OTHERWISE MEET YOUR NEEDS OR EXPECTATIONS.
KB HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, STATUTORY OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO ANY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, NON-INFRINGEMENT, AND FITNESS FOR PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
THE FOREGOING DOES NOT AFFECT ANY WARRANTIES WHICH CANNOT BE EXCLUDED OR LIMITED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW.
Limitation on Liability
IN NO EVENT WILL KB, ITS AFFILIATES, OR ANY LICENSORS, SERVICE PROVIDERS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, OFFICERS OR DIRECTORS OF THE FOREGOING BE LIABLE FOR DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, UNDER ANY LEGAL THEORY, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE, OR INABILITY TO USE, THE WEBSITE, ANY WEBSITES LINKED TO IT, ANY CONTENT ON THE WEBSITE, OR ANY SERVICES OR ITEMS OBTAINED THROUGH THE WEBSITE, INCLUDING ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO PERSONAL INJURY, PAIN AND SUFFERING, EMOTIONAL DISTRESS, LOSS OF REVENUE, LOSS OF PROFITS, LOSS OF BUSINESS OR ANTICIPATED SAVINGS, LOSS OF USE, LOSS OF GOODWILL, OR LOSS OF DATA, AND WHETHER CAUSED BY TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), BREACH OF CONTRACT, OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF FORESEEABLE.
THE FOREGOING DOES NOT AFFECT ANY LIABILITY WHICH CANNOT BE EXCLUDED OR LIMITED UNDER APPLICABLE LAW.
Indemnification
You agree to defend, indemnify, and hold harmless KB and its affiliates, licensors, and service providers, and its and their respective officers, directors, employees, contractors, agents, licensors, suppliers, successors, and assigns, from and against any claims, liabilities, damages, judgments, awards, losses, costs, expenses, or fees (including reasonable attorneys' fees) arising out of or relating to your violation of these Terms of Use or your use of the Website, including, but not limited to, any use of the Website's content, services, or products other than as expressly authorized in these Terms of Use or your use of any information obtained from the Website.
Governing Law and Jurisdiction
All matters relating to the Website and these Terms of Use and any dispute or claim arising therefrom or related thereto (in each case, including non-contractual disputes or claims) shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the internal laws of the State of Florida without giving effect to any choice or conflict of law provision or rule (whether of the State of Florida or any other jurisdiction).
Any legal suit, action or proceeding arising out of, or related to, these Terms of Use or the Website shall be instituted exclusively in the Twelfth Judicial Circuit in and for Sarasota County, Florida, located in the City of Sarasota, or the United States District Court for the Middle District of Florida located in the City of Tampa, although KB retains the right to bring any suit, action or proceeding against you for breach of these Terms of Use in your country of residence or any other relevant country. You waive any and all objections to the exercise of jurisdiction over you by such courts and to venue in such courts.
Limitation on Time to File Claims
ANY CAUSE OF ACTION OR CLAIM YOU MAY HAVE ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THESE TERMS OF USE OR THE WEBSITE MUST BE COMMENCED WITHIN ONE (1) YEAR AFTER THE CAUSE OF ACTION ACCRUES, OTHERWISE, SUCH CAUSE OF ACTION OR CLAIM IS PERMANENTLY BARRED.
Waiver and Severability
No waiver of by KB of any term or condition set forth in these Terms of Use shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or condition or a waiver of any other term or condition, and any failure of KB to assert a right or provision under these Terms of Use shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision.
If any provision of these Terms of Use is held by a court or other tribunal of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, illegal, or unenforceable for any reason, such provision shall be eliminated or limited to the minimum extent such that the remaining provisions of the Terms of Use will continue in full force and effect.
Entire Agreement
These Terms of Use and our Privacy Policy constitute the sole and entire agreement between you and KB with respect to the Website and supersede all prior and contemporaneous understandings, agreements, representations, and warranties, both written and oral, with respect to the Website.
Your Comments and Concerns
The Website is operated by KB at 1990 Main Street, Suite 801, Sarasota, FL 34236.
All other feedback, comments, requests for technical support, and other communications relating to the Website should be directed to: .
Our LocationsSarasota Office1990 Main Street, Suite 801Sarasota, FL 34236Phone: 941.365.4617Toll Free: 800.966.8676Fax: 941.954.3207Lakewood Ranch Office9423 Town Center ParkwayLakewood Ranch, FL 34202Phone: 941.365.4617Tampa Office4350 West Cypress StreetMeridian One, Suite 930Tampa, FL 33607Phone: 813.675.8800ShareFile LoginLoginUpload Files8879 & State Authorizationsto a Specific KB Staff MemberSocial MediaContact Us
Kerkering Barberio - Lets Get Started.
Footer Contact form
Full Name*
First
Email*
Phone*Message
Copyright © 2020 | Kerkering, Barberio & Co |
Privacy Statement
|
Terms of Use
Our site uses cookies and other tracking technologies to assist with navigation and your ability to provide feedback, analyze your use of our products and services, assist with our promotional and marketing efforts.Privacy StatementAccept & Close
As we start to wind down 2020, please note the following:
Dear Clients and Friends of Kerkering, Barberio & Co.,
Kerkering Barberio would like to notify you that payments made on the on-line portal will cutoff at 8:00 p.m. on 12/24/2020.  The site will be down for maintenance from 8:00 p.m. 12/24/2020 through 8:00 a.m. on 01/04/2021.
If you have any questions please call 941-365-4617.
Thank You
Close
searchuserclosetwitter-squarefacebook-squarelinkedin-squareinstagram
